http://www.wolo-mfg.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Magento Commerce
YOUR SOURCE FOR HORN, WARNING LIGHTS & INNOVATIVEPRODUCTS FOR VEHICLES, MOTORCYCLES, MARINE & INDUSTRIAL EQUIPMENT.631-242-0333800-645-5808 U.S. & CANADA
LOG IN
LOG OUT
MY ACCOUNT
MY CART
ABOUT US
CONTACT
TECHNICAL QUESTIONS
Part#/Name
SELECT A CATEGORY
HornsAir HornsElectric Replacement HornsHand HeldIndustrial HornsElectronicElectro-Mechanical12-Volt24-Volt36-Volt36/48-Volt48-Volt72-VoltMarine HornsAir HornStainless SteelHand HeldMotorcycle HornsAir HornElectricSpecialty HornsTruck HornsLow PressureHigh PressurePro SeriesHorn AccessoriesTrainTrain HornsHorn & Air SystemOn-Board Systems & AccessoriesCompressor & Tank SystemsAccessories & PartsBack-up AlarmsWarning LightsRotatingStrobeLEDLight BarsMini Light BarsHalogenStrobeLEDFull Light BarsHalogenStrobeLEDHide Away LightsStrobe Hide AwayStrobe Kits 4 BulbsStrobe Kits 6 BulbsAccessoriesLED Hide AwayLED Kits 4 HeadLED Kits 6 HeadAccessoriesOther LightingHand Help LightsVehicle LightsIndustrial LightsSirens and SpeakersSirensSpeakersNew ProductsClearance & RefurbishedReplacement Parts
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Wolo Manufacturing Corp, uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.  Wolo Manufacturing Corp. is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Wolo Manufacturing Corp. may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with any changes. This policy is effective from December 2011.
What we Collect We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including telephone number and email address
demographic information such as mailing address
other information relevant to process your order
What we do with the Information we Gather We require this information to process your order and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
Processing your credit card payment
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
SECURITY:
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Wolo Manufacturing Corp. does not collect any Cookie
Wolo Manufacturing Corp. does not offer links to other websites
CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION:
Wolo Manufacturing Corp. will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.
